[
  { "id": 1, "question": "Traduis: \"acheter (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "buy", "hint": "yub" },
  { "id": 2, "question": "Traduis: \"aller (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "go", "hint": "og" },
  { "id": 3, "question": "Traduis: \"allumer, éclairer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "light", "hint": "htilg" },
  { "id": 4, "question": "Traduis: \"apporter (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "bring", "hint": "gnibr" },
  { "id": 5, "question": "Traduis: \"apprendre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "learn", "hint": "nrael" },
  { "id": 6, "question": "Traduis: \"(s')appuyer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "lean", "hint": "anel" },
  { "id": 7, "question": "Traduis: \"attraper (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "catch", "hint": "htcac" },
  { "id": 8, "question": "Traduis: \"avoir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "have", "hint": "evah" },
  { "id": 9, "question": "Traduis: \"battre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "beat", "hint": "taeb" },
  { "id": 10, "question": "Traduis: \"blesser (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "hurt", "hint": "truh" },
  { "id": 11, "question": "Traduis: \"boire (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "drink", "hint": "knird" },
  { "id": 12, "question": "Traduis: \"briller (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "shine", "hint": "enihs" },
  { "id": 13, "question": "Traduis: \"brûler (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "burn", "hint": "nrub" },
  { "id": 14, "question": "Traduis: \"cacher (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "hide", "hint": "edih" },
  { "id": 15, "question": "Traduis: \"casser (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "break", "hint": "kaerb" },
  { "id": 16, "question": "Traduis: \"chanter (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "sing", "hint": "gnis" },
  { "id": 17, "question": "Traduis: \"choisir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "choose", "hint": "esoohc" },
  { "id": 18, "question": "Traduis: \"coller (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "stick", "hint": "kcits" },
  { "id": 19, "question": "Traduis: \"combattre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "fight", "hint": "thgif" },
  { "id": 20, "question": "Traduis: \"commencer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "begin", "hint": "nigeb" },
  { "id": 21, "question": "Traduis: \"comprendre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "understand", "hint": "dnatsrednu" },

  { "id": 22, "question": "Traduis: \"acheter (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "bought", "hint": "thguob" },
  { "id": 23, "question": "Traduis: \"aller (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "went", "hint": "tnew" },
  { "id": 24, "question": "Traduis: \"allumer, éclairer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "lit", "hint": "til" },
  { "id": 25, "question": "Traduis: \"apporter (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "brought", "hint": "thguorb" },
  { "id": 26, "question": "Traduis: \"apprendre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "learnt", "hint": "tnrael" },
  { "id": 27, "question": "Traduis: \"(s')appuyer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "leant", "hint": "tnale" },
  { "id": 28, "question": "Traduis: \"attraper (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "caught", "hint": "thguac" },
  { "id": 29, "question": "Traduis: \"avoir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "had", "hint": "dah" },
  { "id": 30, "question": "Traduis: \"battre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "beat", "hint": "taeb" },
  { "id": 31, "question": "Traduis: \"blesser (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "hurt", "hint": "truh" },
  { "id": 32, "question": "Traduis: \"boire (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "drank", "hint": "knard" },
  { "id": 33, "question": "Traduis: \"briller (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "shone", "hint": "ehnos" },
  { "id": 34, "question": "Traduis: \"brûler (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "burnt", "hint": "tnrub" },
  { "id": 35, "question": "Traduis: \"cacher (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "hid", "hint": "dih" },
  { "id": 36, "question": "Traduis: \"casser (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "broke", "hint": "ekorb" },
  { "id": 37, "question": "Traduis: \"chanter (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "sang", "hint": "gnas" },
  { "id": 38, "question": "Traduis: \"choisir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "chose", "hint": "esohc" },
  { "id": 39, "question": "Traduis: \"coller (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "stuck", "hint": "kcuts" },
  { "id": 40, "question": "Traduis: \"combattre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "fought", "hint": "thguof" },
  { "id": 41, "question": "Traduis: \"commencer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "began", "hint": "nageb" },
  { "id": 42, "question": "Traduis: \"comprendre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "understood", "hint": "dootsrednu" },

  { "id": 43, "question": "Traduis: \"acheter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "bought", "hint": "thguob" },
  { "id": 44, "question": "Traduis: \"aller (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "gone", "hint": "enog" },
  { "id": 45, "question": "Traduis: \"allumer, éclairer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "lit", "hint": "til" },
  { "id": 46, "question": "Traduis: \"apporter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "brought", "hint": "thguorb" },
  { "id": 47, "question": "Traduis: \"apprendre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "learnt", "hint": "tnrael" },
  { "id": 48, "question": "Traduis: \"(s')appuyer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "leant", "hint": "tnale" },
  { "id": 49, "question": "Traduis: \"attraper (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "caught", "hint": "thguac" },
  { "id": 50, "question": "Traduis: \"avoir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "had", "hint": "dah" },
  { "id": 51, "question": "Traduis: \"battre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "beaten", "hint": "netabe" },
  { "id": 52, "question": "Traduis: \"blesser (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "hurt", "hint": "truh" },
  { "id": 53, "question": "Traduis: \"boire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "drunk", "hint": "kndur" },
  { "id": 54, "question": "Traduis: \"briller (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "shone", "hint": "ehnos" },
  { "id": 55, "question": "Traduis: \"brûler (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "burnt", "hint": "tnrub" },
  { "id": 56, "question": "Traduis: \"cacher (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "hidden", "hint": "neddih" },
  { "id": 57, "question": "Traduis: \"casser (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "broken", "hint": "nekorb" },
  { "id": 58, "question": "Traduis: \"chanter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "sung", "hint": "gnus" },
  { "id": 59, "question": "Traduis: \"choisir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "chosen", "hint": "nesohc" },
  { "id": 60, "question": "Traduis: \"coller (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "stuck", "hint": "kcuts" },
  { "id": 61, "question": "Traduis: \"combattre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "fought", "hint": "thguof" },
  { "id": 62, "question": "Traduis: \"commencer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "begun", "hint": "nugbe" },
  { "id": 63, "question": "Traduis: \"comprendre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "understood", "hint": "dootsrednu" },

  { "id": 64, "question": "Traduis: \"comprendre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "understand", "hint": "udanstner" },
  { "id": 65, "question": "Traduis: \"conduire (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "drive", "hint": "ervdi" },
  { "id": 66, "question": "Traduis: \"conduire (monter) (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "ride", "hint": "deri" },
  { "id": 67, "question": "Traduis: \"construire (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "build", "hint": "diblu" },
  { "id": 68, "question": "Traduis: \"couler (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "sink", "hint": "inks" },
  { "id": 69, "question": "Traduis: \"courir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "run", "hint": "unr" },
  { "id": 70, "question": "Traduis: \"couter (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "cost", "hint": "tsoc" },
  { "id": 71, "question": "Traduis: \"creuser (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "dig", "hint": "gdi" },
  { "id": 72, "question": "Traduis: \"dépenser (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "spend", "hint": "sdnep" },
  { "id": 73, "question": "Traduis: \"dessiner (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "draw", "hint": "ward" },
  { "id": 74, "question": "Traduis: \"devenir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "become", "hint": "cmeobe" },
  { "id": 75, "question": "Traduis: \"dire (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "say", "hint": "asy" },
  { "id": 76, "question": "Traduis: \"distribuer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "deal", "hint": "aeld" },
  { "id": 77, "question": "Traduis: \"donner (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "give", "hint": "egiv" },
  { "id": 78, "question": "Traduis: \"dormir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "sleep", "hint": "epsle" },
  { "id": 79, "question": "Traduis: \"éclater (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "burst", "hint": "tsrub" },
  { "id": 80, "question": "Traduis: \"écrire (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "write", "hint": "etwir" },
  { "id": 81, "question": "Traduis: \"enseigner (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "teach", "hint": "hcate" },
  { "id": 82, "question": "Traduis: \"entendre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "hear", "hint": "aher" },
  { "id": 83, "question": "Traduis: \"envoyer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "send", "hint": "sdne" },
  { "id": 84, "question": "Traduis: \"comprendre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "understood", "hint": "dnstoouer" },
  { "id": 85, "question": "Traduis: \"conduire (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "drove", "hint": "verdo" },
  { "id": 86, "question": "Traduis: \"conduire (monter) (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "rode", "hint": "deor" },
  { "id": 87, "question": "Traduis: \"construire (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "built", "hint": "tulib" },
  { "id": 88, "question": "Traduis: \"couler (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "sank", "hint": "anks" },
  { "id": 89, "question": "Traduis: \"courir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "ran", "hint": "nar" },
  { "id": 90, "question": "Traduis: \"couter (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "cost", "hint": "tsoc" },
  { "id": 91, "question": "Traduis: \"creuser (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "dug", "hint": "gdu" },
  { "id": 92, "question": "Traduis: \"dépenser (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "spent", "hint": "tneps" },
  { "id": 93, "question": "Traduis: \"dessiner (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "drew", "hint": "werd" },
  { "id": 94, "question": "Traduis: \"devenir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "became", "hint": "mecabe" },
  { "id": 95, "question": "Traduis: \"dire (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "said", "hint": "dias" },
  { "id": 96, "question": "Traduis: \"distribuer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "dealt", "hint": "taled" },
  { "id": 97, "question": "Traduis: \"donner (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "gave", "hint": "evag" },
  { "id": 98, "question": "Traduis: \"dormir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "slept", "hint": "teslp" },
  { "id": 99, "question": "Traduis: \"éclater (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "burst", "hint": "tsrub" },
  { "id": 100, "question": "Traduis: \"écrire (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "wrote", "hint": "tewor" },
  { "id": 101, "question": "Traduis: \"enseigner (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "taught", "hint": "htguat" },
  { "id": 102, "question": "Traduis: \"entendre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "heard", "hint": "daher" },
  { "id": 103, "question": "Traduis: \"envoyer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "sent", "hint": "ents" },
  { "id": 104, "question": "Traduis: \"comprendre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "understood", "hint": "dnstoouer" },
  { "id": 105, "question": "Traduis: \"conduire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "driven", "hint": "rvnied" },
  { "id": 106, "question": "Traduis: \"conduire (monter) (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "ridden", "hint": "ddenir" },
  { "id": 107, "question": "Traduis: \"construire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "built", "hint": "tulib" },
  { "id": 108, "question": "Traduis: \"couler (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "sunk", "hint": "unks" },
  { "id": 109, "question": "Traduis: \"courir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "run", "hint": "unr" },
  { "id": 110, "question": "Traduis: \"couter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "cost", "hint": "tsoc" },
  { "id": 111, "question": "Traduis: \"creuser (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "dug", "hint": "gdu" },
  { "id": 112, "question": "Traduis: \"dépenser (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "spent", "hint": "tneps" },
  { "id": 113, "question": "Traduis: \"dessiner (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "drawn", "hint": "anwrd" },
  { "id": 114, "question": "Traduis: \"devenir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "become", "hint": "cmeobe" },
  { "id": 115, "question": "Traduis: \"dire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "said", "hint": "dias" },
  { "id": 116, "question": "Traduis: \"distribuer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "dealt", "hint": "taled" },
  { "id": 117, "question": "Traduis: \"donner (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "given", "hint": "evign" },
  { "id": 118, "question": "Traduis: \"dormir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "slept", "hint": "teslp" },
  { "id": 119, "question": "Traduis: \"éclater (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "burst", "hint": "tsrub" },
  { "id": 120, "question": "Traduis: \"écrire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "written", "hint": "entwrit" },
  { "id": 121, "question": "Traduis: \"enseigner (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "taught", "hint": "htguat" },
  { "id": 122, "question": "Traduis: \"entendre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "heard", "hint": "daher" },
  { "id": 123, "question": "Traduis: \"envoyer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "sent", "hint": "ents" },
  { "id": 124, "question": "Traduis: \"être (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "been", "hint": "neeb" },
{ "id": 125, "question": "Traduis: \"être assis (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "sat", "hint": "tas" },
{ "id": 126, "question": "Traduis: \"être debout (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "stood", "hint": "dots" },
{ "id": 127, "question": "Traduis: \"être étendu, couché (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "lain", "hint": "nial" },
{ "id": 128, "question": "Traduis: \"s'éveiller (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "awoken", "hint": "wonaek" },
{ "id": 129, "question": "Traduis: \"faire (exécuter) (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "done", "hint": "node" },
{ "id": 130, "question": "Traduis: \"faire (fabriquer) (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "made", "hint": "edam" },
{ "id": 131, "question": "Traduis: \"fermer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "shut", "hint": "tush" },
{ "id": 132, "question": "Traduis: \"frapper (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "hit", "hint": "ith" },
{ "id": 133, "question": "Traduis: \"gâcher, gâter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "spoilt", "hint": "plotsi" },
{ "id": 134, "question": "Traduis: \"gagner (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "won", "hint": "now" },
{ "id": 135, "question": "Traduis: \"garder (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "kept", "hint": "tepk" },
{ "id": 136, "question": "Traduis: \"geler (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "frozen", "hint": "zerofn" },
{ "id": 137, "question": "Traduis: \"glisser (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "slid", "hint": "dils" },
{ "id": 138, "question": "Traduis: \"grandir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "grown", "hint": "wrong" },
{ "id": 139, "question": "Traduis: \"interdire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "forbidden", "hint": "dinfobier" },
{ "id": 140, "question": "Traduis: \"jeter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "thrown", "hint": "nowrht" },
{ "id": 141, "question": "Traduis: \"jurer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "sworn", "hint": "ronsw" },
{ "id": 142, "question": "Traduis: \"lier, attacher (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "bound", "hint": "dunob" },
{ "id": 143, "question": "Traduis: \"lire (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "read", "hint": "dare" },

{ "id": 144, "question": "Traduis: \"manger (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "eat", "hint": "tae" },
{ "id": 145, "question": "Traduis: \"mener (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "lead", "hint": "deal" },
{ "id": 146, "question": "Traduis: \"mettre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "put", "hint": "tup" },
{ "id": 147, "question": "Traduis: \"montrer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "show", "hint": "owhs" },
{ "id": 148, "question": "Traduis: \"mordre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "bite", "hint": "etib" },
{ "id": 149, "question": "Traduis: \"nager (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "swim", "hint": "imsw" },
{ "id": 150, "question": "Traduis: \"nourrir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "feed", "hint": "deef" },
{ "id": 151, "question": "Traduis: \"obtenir (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "get", "hint": "teg" },
{ "id": 152, "question": "Traduis: \"oublier (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "forget", "hint": "togref" },
{ "id": 153, "question": "Traduis: \"pardonner (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "forgive", "hint": "evigrof" },
{ "id": 154, "question": "Traduis: \"parier (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "bet", "hint": "teb" },
{ "id": 155, "question": "Traduis: \"parler (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "speak", "hint": "kepas" },
{ "id": 156, "question": "Traduis: \"payer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "pay", "hint": "ayp" },
{ "id": 157, "question": "Traduis: \"pendre, accrocher (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "hang", "hint": "gnah" },
{ "id": 158, "question": "Traduis: \"penser (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "think", "hint": "kniht" },
{ "id": 159, "question": "Traduis: \"perdre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "lose", "hint": "esol" },
{ "id": 160, "question": "Traduis: \"pleurer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "weep", "hint": "peew" },
{ "id": 161, "question": "Traduis: \"plier (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "bend", "hint": "dneb" },
{ "id": 162, "question": "Traduis: \"porter, supporter (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "bear", "hint": "raeb" },
{ "id": 163, "question": "Traduis: \"poser, déposer (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "lay", "hint": "yal" },
{ "id": 164, "question": "Traduis: \"prendre (infinitif)\" ?", "answer": "take", "hint": "ekat" },

{ "id": 165, "question": "Traduis: \"manger (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "ate", "hint": "tea" },
{ "id": 166, "question": "Traduis: \"mener (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "led", "hint": "del" },
{ "id": 167, "question": "Traduis: \"mettre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "put", "hint": "tup" },
{ "id": 168, "question": "Traduis: \"montrer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "showed", "hint": "dewohs" },
{ "id": 169, "question": "Traduis: \"mordre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "bit", "hint": "tib" },
{ "id": 170, "question": "Traduis: \"nager (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "swam", "hint": "masw" },
{ "id": 171, "question": "Traduis: \"nourrir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "fed", "hint": "def" },
{ "id": 172, "question": "Traduis: \"obtenir (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "got", "hint": "tog" },
{ "id": 173, "question": "Traduis: \"oublier (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "forgot", "hint": "togrof" },
{ "id": 174, "question": "Traduis: \"pardonner (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "forgave", "hint": "evagrof" },
{ "id": 175, "question": "Traduis: \"parier (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "bet", "hint": "teb" },
{ "id": 176, "question": "Traduis: \"parler (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "spoke", "hint": "ekops" },
{ "id": 177, "question": "Traduis: \"payer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "paid", "hint": "diap" },
{ "id": 178, "question": "Traduis: \"pendre, accrocher (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "hung", "hint": "gnuh" },
{ "id": 179, "question": "Traduis: \"penser (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "thought", "hint": "thguoht" },
{ "id": 180, "question": "Traduis: \"perdre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "lost", "hint": "tsol" },
{ "id": 181, "question": "Traduis: \"pleurer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "wept", "hint": "tpew" },
{ "id": 182, "question": "Traduis: \"plier (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "bent", "hint": "tneb" },
{ "id": 183, "question": "Traduis: \"porter, supporter (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "bore", "hint": "erob" },
{ "id": 184, "question": "Traduis: \"poser, déposer (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "laid", "hint": "dial" },
{ "id": 185, "question": "Traduis: \"prendre (Simple past)\" ?", "answer": "took", "hint": "koot" },

{ "id": 186, "question": "Traduis: \"manger (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "eaten", "hint": "neate" },
{ "id": 187, "question": "Traduis: \"mener (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "led", "hint": "del" },
{ "id": 188, "question": "Traduis: \"mettre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "put", "hint": "tup" },
{ "id": 189, "question": "Traduis: \"montrer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "shown", "hint": "wnosh" },
{ "id": 190, "question": "Traduis: \"mordre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "bitten", "hint": "nettib" },
{ "id": 191, "question": "Traduis: \"nager (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "swum", "hint": "musw" },
{ "id": 192, "question": "Traduis: \"nourrir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "fed", "hint": "def" },
{ "id": 193, "question": "Traduis: \"obtenir (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "got", "hint": "tog" },
{ "id": 194, "question": "Traduis: \"oublier (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "forgotten", "hint": "nettorgof" },
{ "id": 195, "question": "Traduis: \"pardonner (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "forgiven", "hint": "nevigrof" },
{ "id": 196, "question": "Traduis: \"parier (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "bet", "hint": "teb" },
{ "id": 197, "question": "Traduis: \"parler (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "spoken", "hint": "nekops" },
{ "id": 198, "question": "Traduis: \"payer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "paid", "hint": "diap" },
{ "id": 199, "question": "Traduis: \"pendre, accrocher (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "hung", "hint": "gnuh" },
{ "id": 200, "question": "Traduis: \"penser (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "thought", "hint": "thguoht" },
{ "id": 201, "question": "Traduis: \"perdre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "lost", "hint": "tsol" },
{ "id": 202, "question": "Traduis: \"pleurer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "wept", "hint": "tpew" },
{ "id": 203, "question": "Traduis: \"plier (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "bent", "hint": "tneb" },
{ "id": 204, "question": "Traduis: \"porter, supporter (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "born", "hint": "nrob" },
{ "id": 205, "question": "Traduis: \"poser, déposer (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "laid", "hint": "dial" },
{ "id": 206, "question": "Traduis: \"prendre (Past participle)\" ?", "answer": "taken", "hint": "nek at" }



]

